chelseamegastore.com 2008-12-17

# Chelsea - the only official online Megastore!

Your Privacy

This document explains our policy regarding any personal information you might supply to us when you visit this site. Our goal is to protect your information.

**Consent**

By accessing or using this website, you agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy of Kitbag Limited (“Kitbag” or “us”), as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We may change our Privacy Policy and security policy from time to time. Please visit this page often for updates and changes. Regardless of later changes or updates, Kitbag will not use your information in a new way without first notifying you of any such changes in the proposed use and obtaining your consent to such use where required to do so by law.

**Collection of Personal Information**

When you engage in certain activities on this site, such as registering, ordering products, or entering contests, Kitbag may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, we may require that you provide us with personal information about yourself, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone number and date of birth. When ordering products on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number.

Kitbag collects all personal information as agent for Chelsea Village Merchandising Limited (“CVML”).

Kitbag collects personal information from you in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. If you order a product, for example, the information is used to mail to you the items ordered and to provide you with any benefits that may be made available to registered users. If you enter a contest, information is collected to qualify the entry and contact you regarding the contest or prize awards. Where you have consented to our doing so, we may also use the personal information you provide to us to inform you of other products and special offers from Kitbag and/or provide your personal information to CVML, Chelsea Football Club and their affiliates or to other carefully selected companies or organisations in order that they may inform you of their products and services.

In order to use your personal information in the manner set out above, we may share that information with affiliates of Kitbag and with CVML, Chelsea Football Club and their affiliates provided that the same are located within the EU.

Your personal information is password-protected to prevent unauthorised access to it. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. 

**Use of Cookies on our site**

When you visit Kitbag, you can surf the site anonymously and access important information without revealing your identity. However, in order to provide better service, we may use "cookies" to track your visit.

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are.

A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number.

Two types of cookies are used on this website:

**Session Cookies**

which are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site

**Persistent cookies**

which remain in the cookie file of your browser for much longer (though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie).

Cookies can help a website to arrange content to match your preferred interests more quickly. Most major websites use cookies. Cookies cannot be used by themselves to identify you.

Find out more about [cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/).

**How we use Cookies on our Site and what Information we collect.**

**Session Cookies.**

  * To allow you to carry information across pages of our site and avoid having to re-enter information.
  * Within registration to allow you to access stored information.
  * To apply discounts dependant on your point of entry into the site.

**Persistent Cookies.**

  * To allow you to maintain a shopping basket.
  * To help us recognise you as a unique visitor (just a number) when you return to our website and to allow us to tailor content to match your preferences. This also prevents you from having to ‘Log In’ every visit.

The cookie cannot be read by a website other than the one that sent the cookie.

**Disabling/Enabling Cookies.**

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you will not be able to use all the interactive features of our site if cookies are disabled.

[Find out how to disable/enable cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/).

**Data Protection**

CVML and Kitbag are registered in accordance with United Kingdom Data Protection Legislation and will hold and use your personal data strictly in accordance with UK data protection legislation.

**Your rights to access your personal information**

You have the right to receive a copy of the personal information that is held about you. You may request a copy of this information by contacting Kitbag’s Data Protection Officer by any of the methods set out below. Kitbag may charge a small fee towards the cost of administering any request you make.

**Updating your information**

In the event that there is a change to your personal information, for example your contact details, please let us know by contacting Kitbag at the address set out below so that we can keep your information up to date and accurate.

**How to contact us**

If you would like any further information or have any comments about our privacy policy, please contact our Data Protection Officer by any of the methods shown below.

By telephone: +44(0)115 9071853

By email: customerservice@kitbag.com

By mail:  
Data Protection Officer  
PO Box 6794  
Derby  
England  
DE7 8EF  

**How does Kitbag protect visitor information?**

Kitbag has a committed Security Policy. Kitbag will retain copies of the information provided when you register on the website, order any products from the site and enter into any competitions. Kitbag implements a number of sophisticated security measures to ensure the safety of any personal information provided. The information is contained on a secure server, which is accessible only by a limited number of employees who have authorised access rights to such information. All sensitive and credit card information supplied by any visitor to chelseamegastore.com is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. SSL is commonly-used for managing the security of message transmission on the Internet through public-and-private key encryption and a digital certificate that establishes your credentials when doing Internet business or other on-line transactions. This certificate is issued by a certification authority, in our case Verisign. To see the certificate for this site click Verisign here. When you are asked to enter any personal details or credit card information the website will be secure. This is easily identifiable by an icon in the bottom of the browser window resembling an unbroken key or a closed lock. SSL ensures that the information being sent is secure. Your card number will be encrypted and replaced by a unique transaction reference number. Kitbag uses online bank secure servers provided by DataCash and does not hold any customer card details on any Kitbag server at any time. To remove any name and address details please see remove details section in the Kitbags help menu.

**Kitbag's Policy for Children**

Kitbag realises and understands that many children will visit the Chelsea Megastore but encourages all persons under 13 to consult with their parents or legal guardian before submitting any information to this website and indeed any other website. However, Kitbag believes that ultimately it is the responsibility of parents or legal guardian to supervise children when online and recommend that parental control tools be put in place. No information collected from anyone under the age of 18 will be used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatever as is stated when you register for competitions or promotions. Although anyone under the age of 13 is able to participate in competitions and promotions, notification of a win or prize will be sent directly to the parent or legal guardian identified in the initial registration process. Any publication of a competition winner's personal details for visitors under 18 will require parental or legal guardian consent during registration.
